One, two, three.
Hello
I promise you, I'm to the end of time
I'll house and fight with a man
We dance inside your hood
And if you leave me in the morning
I'll have such a such a lonely heart
Oh I
Such a lovely fly
If you can fight another reason to stay
Then I know I'm gonna always have a lonely lonely lonely lonely
Your precious heart can't watch it break
So I close my eyes while you walk away
Can I have a second chance?
Can I have another dance?
Can I start another life with you?
Yeah, when I wake up in a haze
And I have a second day's
A thousand miles away
With such a lonely heart
Oh, oh, oh
If you can find another reason to stay
Then I know I'm gonna always have a lonely, lonely, lonely
Oh, oh, oh
Lonely, if it is nothing new, nothing new to me
Nothing new to me
Nothing new, nothing new to you
Lonely, if it is nothing new, nothing new to me
Nothing new to me
Nothing new to you
Mm, oh, oh
Start your lonely life
Oh, oh, oh
If you can find another reason to stay
Then I know I'm gonna always have it lonely, lonely, lonely
Oh, oh, oh, oh
You
The sun was setting behind the distant mountains,
casting a warm glow over the tranquil valley below.
Birds chirp softly in the trees, and a gentle breeze rust-tilted the leaves.
As the evening descended, the sky turned into a canvass of vibrant colors,
painting the horizon with shades of orange, pink and purple.
It was a peaceful scene, a moment of serenity amidst the chaos of the world.